Guide to the collection of mail order erotica, circa 1966-2000
Mail order erotica, circa 1966-2000
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection of mail order erotica, circa 1966-2000
7634
1 cubic ft.
Publications, printed material.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Miscellaneous mail order brochures, fliers, advertisements, and clippings relating to pornographic and erotic videos, photographs, publications, sexual aids and other erotic merchandise aimed at heterosexuals and gay men.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Miscellaneous mail order brochures, fliers, advertisements, and clippings relating to pornographic and erotic videos, photographs, publications, sexual aids and other erotic merchandise aimed at heterosexuals and gay men.
SUBJECTS
Subjects:
Advertising--Sex-oriented businesses.; Pornography.; Bondage (Sexual behavior).; Erotic films.; Erotica.; Gay men--sexual behavior.; Heterosexuals--sexual behavior.; Leather lifestyle.; Mail-order business.; Sadomasochism.; Sex oriented periodicals.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
CONTAINER LIST
- Promotional material mostly for gay male erotic magazines and photographs, collected by the Mariposa Foundation, circa 1966-1970s (Box 1, Folder 1-17)
- S&M Dungeon Devices, collected by Mariposa Foundation, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Pat Rocco catalogs, no. 24-26, collected by Mariposa Foundation, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Calafran catalogs, 3 issues, collected by Mariposa Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Various catalogs, including a 1972 catalog of marital aids by Le Salon Mail Order, catalogs by Rodox Trading of Denmark, International Guild Guides, and assorted catalogs of gay male erotica, collected by Mariposa Foundation., circa 1971- 1980s (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Zimba Productions, photo studio presenting the black male physique, circa 1980s? (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Demand, by Wings. Audio cassettes and videos., circa 1980s? (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Katsam Productions, gay porn videos, collected by Elysian Fields Booksellers, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Mercury Distributing, no. 1. San Francisco gay oriented products, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Mercury Mail Order, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Video Wholesale Movies, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cross Country, poster for Falcon studios movie, circa 1990s? (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Sensations catalogs, 3 issues, collected by Cornell, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Pacific Creek Associates, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bondage Annual, Anonymous 2006 gift, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bondage Toy Catalog, Anonymous 2006 gift (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Promotional material for heterosexual and transvestite bondage magazines and videos, Anonymous 2006 gift., 1978-circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Damsels in Distress, Buyer's Guide, no. 1. B&D Pleasures. Anonymous 2006 gift, circa 1990s (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Buyer's Guide, fetish catalog and supplement, B&D Pleasures. Anonymous 2006 gift., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Complete Adult Mail Order Catalog, Anonymous 2006 gift., circa 1980 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Lorell Dolan Productions, panty and bra lingerie videos. Anonymous 2006 gift., circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Music Legs, ca. 2000s (Box 1)
- Music Legs, ca. 2000s (Box 1)
  Apparel, leggings, pantyhose, costumes.
- Tu Shy, Spring 2006 (Box 1)
  Apparel
- Foreplay, Volume 1, January 2007 (Box 1)
- Body Zone, Volume X1, October 2006 (Box 1)